CURRICULUM VITAE

Kaushal Pandey (SDE)

Address: 38'C Vaibhav Nagar Extension

Kanadiya Road Indore (M.P.) **Mobile No.**: 8770709118

Email-Id: Kaushalpandey455@gmail.com
LinkedIn: kaushal-pandey-067898165

GitHub: https://github.com/KaushalSalvatore

Objective

I would like to describe myself as a person, who wants to keep growing, learn and adapt to the changes occurring around me either it is professionally or personally. I set my goals as a short term and through achieving these short-term goals to a achieve a major goal. I would love to work in an organization that helps to improve myself, facilitating my contribution through thoughts and action to the company's vision and thus achieve self-development by playing a significant role in building the organization.

Summary

I have overall work **4 Year Experience** in software industry. Recently I completed the **Google Data Analytics Professional Certificate.** I am working in **Hiecor Software Technologies Pvt. Ltd**. as Mobile Application developer. I got rich experience in Mobile and web application development. I have excellent understanding of mobile application life cycle and including SQL.

Work Experience

- Working as a Android Developer at **Hiecor Software Technologies Pvt** Ltd in Indore from April 2021 to till date.
- Worded as a Android Developer at Katsam Soft Pvt Ltd in Indore from February 2019 to August 2020.
- Worded as a jr. Android Developer at Idice Systems and Technologies Pvt. Ltd in Indore from July 2017 to October 2018.

Technical Skills		
Operating System	Windows XP/7/8/10/11, Linux	
Languages	Java, Dart, kotlin ,Python (NumPy, Pandas, Matplotlib, Scikit-learn)	
Framework	Android, Flutter, Flask, Django	
Database	SQLite, Postgres, Firebase	
IDE	Android-Studio, Microsoft Virtual Studio, Atom, PyCharm, Anaconda	
BI Tool	Tableau, Power BI	
General Skills	Machine Learning Algorithms, Data Visualization, Data Preparation, Exploratory Data Analysis (EDA), Future Engineering, web scraping, Socket.IO	
Version-Control	Git, Bitbucket	

Educational Qualification

- Master in **Business Information Technology** from Astral Institute of Technology and Research College. Affiliated to DAVV (2019-2021)
- ➤ Bachelor In **Electronic and Instrumentation Engineering** from Shri Vaishnav Institute of Technology and Science College, Affiliated to RGPV (2012-2016)

Certification

Google Data Analytics Professional Certificate: Complete extensive six-month job ready Google Career training, Demonstrated hands on experience with data cleaning, data visualization, project management, interpreting and communicating data analytics findings. Confidence in transforming complex data into actionable and clear insights. Fluency in computer programming languages and a solid understanding of database.

PROJECTS EXECUTED

Project #01	POS (Point of Sale)
Environment	Android Native
Description	Point of Sale is a free Android app that has everything you need for your point of sale, invoicing and customer management. Ring up a sale, generate a quote, setup terms on an invoice, take a deposit, refund an order and sign up a subscription with this app.
Play-store Link	https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.betasoft.hiecorapp

Project #02	HieCOR Customer Facing POS
Environment	Android Native
Description	Paired with the HieCOR Point of Sale, this application will give a customer facing screen showing the order contents as they are rung up. It will allow the customer to input their Phone and/or email address for Loyalty tracking + enable signature, tip collection and receipt delivery.
Play-store Link	https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.hiecor.hiecorposcustomerview

Project #03	тото
Environment	Android Native
Description	This application base on food delivery functionality. In this application Use for customer and restaurant can directly order food and salesman also can take the order from restaurant and hotels.
Play-store Link	https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.totogoodfood.android

Project #04	Investelite
Environment	Android Native
Description	This Application for manage share market records and investment advice, elite report. in this application show the daily share market record.
Play-store Link	https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.katsamsoft.investelitemvp&hl=en

Project #05	IRC (Indore Residency Club)
Environment	Android Native
Description	This mobile application for Club Members of Indore Residency. member can be see All Events of Club and join the event and participate and can check profile, change profile According to category's etc.
Play-store Link	https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.brainware.infosoft.irc

Personal Details

Strengths	 Positive Attitude Adaptability & Flexibility Enthusiasm for learning. 	
Interests	 Photography Watching Movies and Series Playing Video Game 	
Languages	Hindi and English	
Date-Of-Birth	29-09-1995	
Passport No.	S4616811	
Father's Name	Mr. Rajendra Pandey	
Gender	Male	
Nationality	Indian	

Declaration

Place :	Kaushal Pandey

I hereby declare that the details provided above are true the best of my knowledge.